Guide to the James Weldon Johnson Collection Manuscript Miscellany
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
James Weldon Johnson Collection manuscript miscellany
1900-2009
JWJ MSS MISC
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Single manuscripts and small groups of manuscripts, including literary manuscripts, letters, and other documents. Materials are grouped under headings by author or corporate name.
Total Boxes: ongoing
Other Storage Formats: oversize, bound volumes
Linear Feet: ongoing
James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters (Yale University)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ongoing collection of documents acquired by gift and purchase from various sources. Source information is recorded on each folder. For further information, consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research. Restricted Fragile Papers may only be consulted with permission of the appropriate curator. Preservation photocopies for reference use have been substituted in the main files.
Scope and Contents
This finding aid encompasses single manuscripts and small groups of manuscripts acquired by the Beinecke Library from various sources and at various times, which the Library has chosen to describe here rather than as separate entries in Yale University Library's on-line Public Access Catalog (Orbis). These materials include literary manuscripts, individual or small groups of letters, and single documents. Materials are grouped under headings for author or other personal or corporate name to which they most closely relate. Items of unidentified authorship are grouped separately under "Unidentified" at the end of the finding aid. Group numbers were assigned as items were added to the collection; entries appear in alphabetical order by main entry, not in group number order. Within each group, folders (F-[#]) and volumes (V-[#]) are numbered in order of processing.
To request materials listed here, please cite the Miscellany call number, written as JWJ MSS MISC, the group number, and the folder or volume number appearing to the left of the item description. For example, to obtain item F-1 from the materials listed under J. California Cooper, complete an individual call slip as follows:
JWJ MSS MISC
Grp 1, Item F-1
This list is ongoing, and it is subject to revision as new materials are acquired and, on occasion, as groups of manuscripts are removed and cataloged separately as artificial collections. When materials are removed and reclassified, a cross reference to the new call number is placed in the list.
In addition to newly received items which have been described using current cataloging standards, this finding aid contains previoulsy cataloged material. Descriptions for the latter items have been transcribed from card sets in the Manuscript Catalog; these entries are identified by "rec," followed by the year of the conversion, e.g., (rec/97).
African American authors; American literature; Authors, American; James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters (Yale University)
- B
  - BALDWIN, JAMES, 1924-1987
    - "A propos de M. Wilson", 1971 May 29; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item (2 p.); 30 cm. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-1)
      Scope and Contents
      Essay, holograph, on Edmund Wilson, signed at Nice. With typed transcript.
      General note
      Accession: 19820108-a
    - [Malcolm X], [ca. 1969]; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item ([1], 146 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-2)
      Draft, typescript mimeograph, of Baldwin's screenplay based on Alex Haley's The Autobiography of Malcolm X. Differs substantially from version published in 1973 as One Day, When I Was Lost; possibly an earlier draft.
      Inscribed "Background material for screenplay on Malcolm X. Calder Willingham."
      Accession: 20040401-o
    - "Notes for Project: Letter to My Younger Brother", undated; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item (2 leaves); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-3)
      Manuscript, typed and signed, discussing a book project.
      Accession: 20050712-c
    - "The Negro in Paris", [ca. 1950-1952]; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item ([8] leaves); 25 cm. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-4)
      Draft, typescript, of article for The Reporter. Accompanied by three TLS, dating from 1952, to "Mr. Rodman" of The Reporter, all regarding the article, and one ANS to an unidentified recipient.
      Accession: 16025
    - Letter: to Sam[uel L. Blumenfeld], 1953 May 31 and 1954 February 11; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 2 items. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-5)
      One TLS in which Baldwin announces his intention to finish "Letter for My Younger Brother," describes his thoughts on newly begun novel ("Giovanni's Room"), and requests a loan of twenty dollars. The letter includes a clipping of an article on James Baldwin from the Herald Tribune Book Review (1953 May 31).
      Accession: 33780
    - Letter: to Sam[uel L. Blumenfeld], 1953 June 6; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-6)
      One TLS to Samuel L. Blumenfeld written in Paris roughly one month after Baldwin's first book was published.
      Accession: 36974
    - Letter: to Sam[uel L. Blumenfeld], 1954 January 11; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-7)
      One TLS to Samuel L. Blumenfeld, written in Cannes, discussing various writing projects, including Baldwin's new work on a "primer" based on correspondence with his younger brother, completion of "The Amen Corner," and work towards his second novel, Giovanni's Room.
      Accession: 36971
    - Letters: between Sam[uel L. Blumenfeld] and Baldwin, 1956 November 26 and n.y. December 5; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 2 items (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-8)
      One TLS to Samuel L. Blumenfeld, written in Corsica, and one TL to Baldwin from Blumenfeld. Baldwin mentions a new novel (possibly "Another Country"), the reception of "Giovanni's Room," and discusses returning to New York in the Spring of 1957. In his letter Blumenfeld discusses reading "Giovanni's Room" and compliments Baldwin's writing.
      Accession: 36972
    - Letters: to [Edward] Parone, 1955 March 11, July 7, and 1959 January 29; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 3 items (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-9)
      One ALS and two TLS to Edward Parone. Baldwin discusses his play "The Amen Corner"as well as his personal life (such as his financial situation and partner Lucien Happersberger). Includes letter written while Baldwin was at Yaddo and in New York and Washington, D.C.
      Accession: 38554
    - Correspondence with John C. Wilson, 1957-1958; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 17 items (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-10)
      Correspondence regarding a proposed stage adaptation of Baldwin's novel, Giovanni's Room (New York: Dial Press, 1956). Correspondence includes one typescript letter, signed, from Baldwin to Wilson, and one typescript carbon letter from Wilson to Baldwin. Accompanied by 15 letters between between Wilson and others, including Albert I. Da Silva of Reinheimer & Cohen, Frederick L. Keefe of The New Yorker, and representatives of the William Morris Agency.
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Purchased from William Reese Co. (Swann Galleries sale, New York, 2009 February 26, lot 257) on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2009
      General
      Accession: 2009-jwj-27997
    - Letters: to Shawn Henderson, 1977 Park Blvd., Camden, New Jersey 08103, 1985-1986; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 6 items (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-11)
      Correspondence, with accompanying envelopes, includes three autograph letters, signed, two autograph notes, signed, and one page with notes and sketches. Letters discuss writing, books, travel, and other engagements.
      Purchased from William Reese Co. (Swann sale 2342, New York, 2014 March 27, lot 341) on the American Literature Fund, 2014
      Accession: 2014-jwj-10
    - "An Open Letter to My Sister, Angela Y. Davis", 1970 November 19; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987; 1 item (6 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 4, Folder F-12)
      Draft, typescript, corrected, of essay. Differs from version published in The New York Review of Books (January 7, 1971 issue). Signed "Brother James".
      Purchased from Elysium Press on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2015.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0001
  - BARAKA, AMIRI, 1934-2014
    - Junkies Are Full of (SHH...), 1969, 1995 (Box GROUP 48, Folder F-1)
      2 items (34 leaves).
      Accession: 47131
      Purchased from Between the Covers on the Donald Windham-Sandy Campbell Collection Endowment Fund, 2011.
      Drafts, typescript, corrected, signed and dated 1995 (16 l.), and photocopy of typescript, corrected, signed and dated July 30, 1969 (18 l.).
  - BERG, RICHARD.
    - "Shelia", undated; Berg, Dick; 1 item (126 p.); 28.5 cm. (Box GROUP 55, Folder F-1)
      Draft, typescript mimeograph, corrected, of Berg's screenplay for the film Honky. "Shelia" was the working title and source novel title.
      Purchased from Royal Books on The Bradford F. and Lila L. Swan Fund, 2016.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0035
  - BLOSSOM, LAUREL
    - Letter: to Mr. Barreio, 1980 October 27; Blossom, Laurel; 1 item (Box GROUP 35, Folder F-1)
      One TLS regarding Tenth Birthday Party for the Poets and Writers organization.
      Removed from Poets & Writers, Inc.: Tenth Birthday Party. New York: Poets & Writers, Inc., 1980.
      Accession: 33176
  - BRAITHWAITE, WILLIAM STANLEY, 1878-1962
    - Letter: Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Robert Underwood Johnson, New York, New York, 1910 January 20; 1 item: (1 p.); 22 cm. (Box GROUP 67, Folder F-1)
      Autograph letter, signed, regarding submission of verses for The Century Magazine, and the death of Richard Watson Gilder.
      Removed from the Carl Van Vechten Papers, 2017.
  - BRASEL, J.
    - Photographs of African-American men and women by J. Brasel, Muskogee, Indian Territory, undated; Brasel, J.; 6 items; 10.5 x 6.4 cm. (Box GROUP 20, Folder F-1)
      Six carte de visite size photographs of young African- American men and women. Three show women, and three show men; two are bust portraits, while four are full-length portraits with studio props. Probably photographed in the 1870s-80s.
      Accession: 20001011-r
  - BROOKS, GWENDOLYN, 1917-2000
    - Letters and inscriptions: to James E. Kelly, 1985-1986; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; 4 items. (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-1)
      ANS in holiday card thanking Kelly for sharing the "Sheltered Man," in enveloped postmarked 1985 Dec 16; ALS dated 1986 Jan 4, regarding Kelly's artwork; a printed 1979 Chicago Public Library bookmark containing "To Young Readers," a poem by Brooks, inscribed to Kelly and signed by Brooks; and an undated card inscribed to Kelly and signed by Brooks.
      Accession: 19920916-a
    - "Charles", undated; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; 1 item (2 p.); 18 cm. (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-2)
      Poem, four lines, holograph, signed, with 'From "Bronzeville Boys and Girls"' written by Brooks on verso.
      Accession: 19940131-d
    - Letters: to Ely Liebon, 1966 September 2 and undated; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; 3 items (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-3)
      Two ALS and an annotated typescript of a syllabus for the "Chicago Teachers College North Poetry Workshop."
      Accession: 43122
    - Review of "Collected Poems of Langston Hughes.", 1994 October 25; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; 1 item (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-4)
      Autograph manuscript of Brooks' review of "Collected Poems of Langston Hughes" edited by Arnold Rampersad. Brooks provides an overview of the collection and then critiques particular poems. The manuscript is accompanied by a copy of Brooks' letter to the editor regarding the review.
      Accession: 43121
    - Children Coming Home, autograph manuscript, 1990-1991; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; 1 item (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-5)
      Autograph manuscript of a title page and drafts of three poems for Children Coming Home: "Superbe/A Something of My Own," "God is a White Gorilla," and "Richardine: White Girls are Particular People." The manuscript also includes a table of contents for In Montgomery and Other Poems. The manuscript is titled Blacks volume II.
      Accession: 43123
    - Photograph of Gwendolyn Brooks at the 1973 Fourth Annual Illinois Poet Laureate Awards, 1 item. (Box GROUP 5, Folder F-6)
      Gelatin silver black and white photographic print [by Frank Giamboy?] of Gwendolyn Brooks at the Fourth Annual Illinois Poet Laureate Awards held at the University of Chicago in 1973 in Chicago, Illinois. Brooks is shown reading a copy of MAJI: A Journal of the Black Arts, the quarterly publication of MAJI-MAJI Collective at Temple University in Philadelphia, while an unidentified African American man looks on. Also pictured are three other unidentified individuals.
      Purchased from Waiting for Godot Books on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2009.
      Accession: 2009-jwj-33119
  - BYRNE, MARGARET C.
    - "About Post-War Jobs for Negroes", circa 1944; 1 item (3 p.) (Box GROUP 68, Folder F-1)
      Typescript draft of article written for Interracial Review
      Gift of Dorothy Peterson through Carl Van Vechten, 1953
- C
  - CARVER, GEORGE WASHINGTON, 1864?-1943
    - Letter: The Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute, to Ms. Rebecca Caudill, 1926-1927 (Box GROUP 46, Folder F-1)
      4 items.
      Purchased from James Cummins Bookseller on the George B. Alvord Fund, 2011.
      Accession: 45452
      One ALS (December 6, 1926), with TLCS enclosed, comprised of responses to three questions: 1. Does truth exist only in the abstract?; 2. What is necessary to have a knowledge of things, as you spoke of in your informal talk?; 3. Do you believe that God, Truth, beauty, music, nature and science are interchangeable terms, and a worship -- worship in the sense of study and self devotion -- of any particular one of these, is equivalent to a worship of any one of the others?. Accompanied by original envelope (postmarked January 13, 1927).
  - CHESTNUTT, CHARLES WADDELL
    - "Aunt Mimy's Son", [ca. 1900]; Chestnutt, Charles Waddell; 1 item (30 p.); 22 cm. (Box GROUP 11, Folder F-1)
      Short story, holograph, written on the verso of Chestnutt's Cleveland, Ohio stenographer business paper. With ALS dated 1942 Jul 22, from Chestnutt's daughter, Helen M. Chestnutt, Cleveland, Ohio, to Harold Jackman, New York, and ALS dated 1942 Aug 3 to Carl Van Vechten, New York, both regarding the short story.
      Accession: 19431001-a
  - CHRISTIAN, MARK BRUCE, 1900-
    - "The Liberty Monument (in memory of the patriots who fell in the riot of September 14, 1874)", [ca. 1970]; Christian, Mark Bruce, 1900-; 2 items. (Box GROUP 9, Folder F-1)
      Essay, typescript with holograph corrections and additions, and a photocopy of the typescript, with holograph corrections and additions. With a manuscript draft of an announcement regarding publications of the Archives of Negro History in an unidentified hand.
      Accession: 19700921-b
  - COLEMAN, WARREN
    - "Nuremberg U.S.A.", 1964-1965 September 9; Coleman, Warren; 1 item (122 p.); 28.5 cm. (Box GROUP 62, Folder F-1)
      Draft, typescript mimeograph, of Coleman's script for the unproduced play. Laid in is a typed letter, signed, by Coleman addressed to "Frank" stating that a mutual friend, "Ralph", considers the play to be good for production, dated 1965 September 9.
      Purchased from Royal Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2015.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0007
  - CONNELLY, MARC, 1890-1980
    - "Cabin in the Sky", 1942 July 21; Connelly, Marc, 1890-1980; Schrank, Joseph; 1 item (431 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 58, Folder F-1)
      Composite script complete, typescript mimeograph, corrected, of Marc Connelly and Joseph Schrank's screenplay for the film Cabin in the Sky.
      Purchased from Royal Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2016.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0029
  - COOPER, J. CALIFORNIA
    - Letter: to [Eunice] Hickey, 1992 Aug 17; Cooper, J. California; 1 item (1 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 1, Folder F-1)
      TLS, regarding Cooper's work. With blank envelope.
      Accession: 19941216-b
  - CROUSE, CONRAD J.
    - Letter: to Charles Van Natten, Tarrytown, New York, 1889 July 2; Crouse, Conrad J.; 2 items (Box GROUP 40, Folder F-1)
      One ALS enclosing a ticket to J.P. Stenson's Mammoth Pavilion "Uncle Tom's Cabin Co." Drawing of "Uncle Tom" on the envelope.
      Accession: 36534
  - CULLEN, COUNTEE, 1903-1946
    - "To Walter White", October 1943; Cullen, Countee, 1903-1946; 1 item (Box GROUP 53, Folder F-1)
      Poem, autograph manuscript, signed.
      Purchased from Between the Covers on the George B. Alvord Fund, 2016.
      Accession: 2017-jwj-0007
- D
  - DARTMOUTH ALUMNI MAGAZINE
    - Letter: to Thomas Secondo, Enfield, CT, 1991 June 27; Dartmouth Alumni Magazine; 1 item (1 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 24, Folder F-1)
      TLS responding to Mr. Secondo's inquiry about Forrest Bartley Whittaker, Jr., who played basketball for Dartmouth in 1926. Accompanied by: a copy of Whittaker's matriculation card; a copy of a 1953 letter from Dartmouth's alumni office to the Registrar of Vital Statistics in Columbus, Ohio, with reply; copies of pages from the athletics section of the Dartmouth Alumni Magazine, 1926, which mention Whittaker; a carbon copy of Secondo's letter of inquiry to Dartmouth, 1991 June 11; and a copy of The Dartmouth Pictorial, Carnival Number, 1926, which includes a photo of Whittaker.
      Removed from the Randolph Linsly Simpson African-American Collection.
  - DODSON, OWEN, 1914-
    - Papers relating to The Confession Stone: Song Cycles, 1962-1976; Dodson, Owen, 1914-1983; 7 items. (Box GROUP 15, Folder F-1, F-2)
      Forty-nine-page typescript mimeograph copy of "The Confession Stone: Song Cycles," with annotations and corrections in pencil and pen in an unidentified hand, "copyrighted 1965," and bound in a white folder containing manuscript notes in an unidentified hand on the inside back cover; eleven-page typescript carbon of "The Land of the Living and The Land of the Risen Dead," dated 1962 Nov 16; "Mary's Lullaby" printed on a leaf followed by Dodson's reproduced signature and "Christmas, 1963"; oversized picture postcard containing a portrait photograph of Countee Cullen with a note dated 1970 Apr 30 from Dodson to Paul Breman regarding Confession Stone on the verso; typed coctail party invitation to Paul Breman dated 1976 Dec 15, from Dodson and his wife Edith, mimeographed on the verso of a printed holiday card containing the poem "A Certain Glory"; portrait photograph of Dodson by Kurt Ammann; and six undated 9 x 5 cm. cards containing holograph notes for an unidentified lecture.
      Accession: 19980323-a
    - Christmas, 1943; 1 item. (Box GROUP 15, Folder F-3)
      Poem, typescript, signed.
      Gift of Dorothy Burnham, 2014.
      Accession: 2014.jwj.1
  - DOVE, RITA
    - Letters: to Dan Johnson, 1988; Dove, Rita, 1952-; 2 items. (Box GROUP 25, Folder F-1)
      One TLS and one TPcS regarding a presentation copy of Dove's Ten poems.
      Removed from Ten poems (Lisbon: Penumbra Press, 1977).
      Accession: 20010703-y
  - DUNBAR, PAUL LAURENCE, 1872-1906
    - "Harriet Beecher Stowe", before 1898 (Box GROUP 47, Folder F-1)
      1 item (1 p.); 27 cm.
      Accession: 2012.jwj.15
      Purchased from the William Reese Company on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2012.
      Custodial History
      From the collection of Marjorie Wiggin Prescott.
      Sonnet, autograph manuscript, signed, printers' copy. Published in Century Magazine (November 1898).
    - "A Plantation Portrait", before 1901 (Box GROUP 47, Folder F-2)
      Accession: 27989
      Purchased from William Reese Company on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2009.
      Poem, draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, signed "P.L.D." Published in The Saturday Evening Post (1901).
      1 item (1 l.); 28 cm.
- F
  - FOREMAN, CARL
    - "High Noon", 1949 January 2 - February 7; Foreman, Carl; 1 item (122 p.); 27.25 cm. (Box GROUP 61, Folder F-1)
      Draft, typescript mimeograph, corrected, of Berg's screenplay for the film Home of the Brave. "High Noon" was the working title. Thirteen 8 x 10 photographs from the film are bound-in.
      Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 2015.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0020
  - FREDERICK DOUGLASS CREATIVE ARTS CENTER
    - 16th Annual Black Roots Festival program, circa 1985; Frederick Douglass Creative Arts Center; 1 item (8 p.); 22 cm. (Box GROUP 51, Folder F-1)
      Printed program for 16th annual festival honoring James Baldwin and John O. Killens.
      Purchased from Heritage Book Shop, Inc. on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2001
      Removed from Fifth Sunday (Lexington: University of Kentucky, 1985) by Rita Dove.
      Accession: 2001-jwj-1
  - FROST, LEE, 1935-2007
    - "The Man with Two Heads", 1972 February 10-19; Frost, Lee, 1935-2007; 1 item (128 p.); 28.5 cm. (Box GROUP 64, Folder F-1)
      Draft, typescript mimeograph, corrected, of Frost and Wes Bishop's screenplay for the film The Thing with Two Heads. "The Man with Two Heads" was the working title. The copy likely belonged to Roosevelt "Rosey" Grier, whose name is written on the front wrapper.
      Accession: 2016-jwj-0012
- G
  - GARDEN, MARY, 1874-1967
    - Letter: New York, to Hall Johnson, 1933 Mar 3; Garden, Mary, 1874-1967; 1 item (3 p.); 18 cm. (Box GROUP 16, Folder F-1)
      ALS regarding "Run, Little Chillun."
      Accession: 19660403-a
  - GORDIMER, NADINE
    - Letter: Johannesburg, South Africa, to William Johnston, 1963 Jun 30; Gordimer, Nadine, 1923-2014; 1 item (2 p.); 34 cm. (Box GROUP 12, Folder F-1)
      TLS regarding The Classic Johannesburg Quarterly, a literary magazine for which Gordimer served as a trustee. With a printed subscription form and a typed description of the publication.
      Accession: 19821201-a
- H
  - H. M. VELIE'S COLORED SONG BIRDS AND CONCERT CO.
    - Printed material, 1896, undated; H. M. Velie's Colored Song Birds and Concert Co.; 3 items. (Box GROUP 31, Folder F-1)
      Materials include a broadside for a 1896 tour and hotel and theater contracts, completed in manuscript.
      Accession: 14882
  - HALEY, ALEX
    - "For T.V. Guide", undated; Haley, Alex, 1921-1992; 1 item (2 leaves); 22 cm. (Box GROUP 32, Folder F-1)
      Holograph manuscript draft of article, corrected, for T.V. Guide on "Roots" program. Accompanied by clipping of cover, signed, for October 1976 issue of the Journal of the Film and Television Arts.
      Accession: 21242
  - HAMMERSTEIN, OSCAR, 1895-1960
    - "Carmen Jones", [ca. 1945]; Hammerstein, Oscar, II, 1895-1960; 1 item (84 p.); 28 cm. (Box GROUP 14, Folder F-1)
      Libretto, mimeograph typescript, with cover containing the label of the Rialto Mimeographing and Typing Service Bureau, New York.
      Accession: 19860414-d
  - HANDY, W. C. (WILLIAM CHRISTOPHER), 1873-1958
    - Letter: New York, to Rodney A. Coleman, 1956 Aug 17; Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1873-1958; 1 item (1 p.); 27 cm. (Box GROUP 17, Folder F-1)
      TLS which accompanied material that Handy autographed for Coleman. Accompanied by a sheet on which is affixed a photograph of Handy clipped from an unidentified publication, four W. C. Handy commemorative postage stamps, and an envelope postmarked Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, with a first day issue Booker T. Washington postage stamp; a signature of Handy cut from an unidentified document is glued to the front of the envelope.
      Accession: 19721201-g
  - HEYWARD, DOROTHY, 1890-1961